what's up periscope hey does this show
on Twitter automatically yeah probably
my cool welcome welcome welcome welcome
to the e on shipping party
Oh like I said we have 20 eons built so
far those are the 20 don't worry they
won't ship to you like that
these are q8a eons for us just testing
out the provisioning script making sure
they're all good we literally got
everybody at this party these are the
boxes Aeons will be coming in there's a
lot you just don't realize it how many
of something is something not too late
it's not too late over nyan Q aim right
now fine here's the assembly team right
here
getting a few more a few more amounts of
printed you want to make sure you guys
got the right mounts fury on oh it's a
party out it's a party these are the
four that go Annie on so they're got to
assemble own every on is tested
has anyone Akama made a neon drive a car
of course hope you guys watched our
periscope how many yards are being
shipped way too many you know I
submitted to all of them it's a little
you are must you know what you do is you
just say I'm Twitter that we're shipping
tomorrow and guess why everyone kind of
ship tomorrow yeah but now the more
people are buying them so it's getting
harder to ship is probably selling water
shop that coming i buy a on fire on fire
come on every on you buy you make them
work harder we're at Christmas party
last night so today we have the shipping
party oh so these are the cables they'll
be included with your Eon well he owns
come with a long cable the short cable
they come with GoPro mounts heat sinks
are all measured to make sure they're
the correct size there are no comma
lighter and lighter is a scam folks
every on has hand applied thermal paste
for maximum conductivity cleaned
polished
giggle the box as a phone came in you
ever opened hundreds of boxes of phones
they used to like their boxes right
right there's a lot of useful life
before I work to come when you unbox 100
of the same phone it's less fun what
periscope alliance of show you iam
number 11 I wouldn't go to you number 11
let's go I gotta hide you from over here
because there's secrets on the
whiteboard super secrets oneplus still
producing three keys I don't think so
over the meeting room quality of growth
maybe we should maybe we should put them
all in the meeting room that dashed bit
let's put everything in the meeting room
that'll be the final packing room then
to like final pack oh you want to pair
with the label pen all right 128 gig
Yeon's those are those are coming out
soon I'm so young number 11 is in this
box here well I think this one here
we can see the serial number fresh every
you know will be wiped out with a
microfiber cloth oh if you guys haven't
seen the little Aeon change we made a
tiny last minute hardware change of this
my young CVE three holes
that's so your yawn can have a light
sensor and it can dynamically adjust its
brightness depending on how bright it is
see how it gets dimmer and now it gets
brighter those are all 64gb on the 128
are coming out in a little bit I'll have
to go down to the factory and talk to
them yeah let's see let's see how many
young to be sold to that oh man guys you
know yawns are flying off the shelves
this is the end of year whiteboard these
are the last things we got a test on
every yawn we're gonna test the fan
we're gonna test the camera we're gonna
test the USB port with the Android
self-driving cars and we ship if you
haven't heard about self-driving car
Awareness Week and the self-driving car
awareness tour go on our Twitter
twitter.com slash comma underscore AI it
is the pin tweet why don't have a big
but sales data secret we gotta have some
secrets to come AI right though we do
have we do some cool monitors but yeah
if you haven't heard self-driving car
awareness tour um what I've said about
press we got a few reach outs from SF
press we're not doing SF press this time
um but we are happy to do local press in
the stops we make on the self-driving
car awareness tour we'd love to give you
guys a demo of our open source software
open pilot running on the latest comet a
I hardware try it out we have the stock
system ready for you to try as well so
you can really get a a be comparison to
see why open pilot is the future cool
any last questions
yeah so eons are hopefully yeah they
should about today hopefully everybody
if everybody does their part it all
comes together
shipping yesterday wasn't outside gone
with us he's in New York man he's
already in New York cool thanks for
watching